=Half-awake=
نصف مستيقظ
=Episode 5=
=الحلقة 5=
Gu Yixiao,
قو ييشياو,
I've figured it out.
لقد فهمت الأمر.
Since you won't let me go,
بما أنك لن تدعني أذهب،
and I'm destined to stay by your side,
ومقدر لي أن أبقى بجانبك،
then maybe starting now,
ربما نبدأ الآن،
I'll try to like you.
سأحاول أن أحبك.
Really?
حقًا؟
You're so obedient?
أنت مطيعٌ للغاية؟
What trick are you playing this time?
ما هي الحيلة التي ستلعبها هذه المرة؟
I'm not playing any tricks on you.
أنا لا أخدعك.
After what happened last night,
بعد ما حدث الليلة الماضية،
I'm exhausted.
أنا مرهق.
I don't want to fight anymore.
لا أريد القتال بعد الآن.
I just want life to be a little better.
أريد فقط أن تكون الحياة أفضل قليلاً.
Gu Yixiao,
قو ييشياو,
if I learn to behave well,
إذا تعلمت أن أتصرف بشكل جيد،
can you treat me better?
هل يمكنك أن تعاملني بشكل أفضل؟
Sure. (Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org)
بالتأكيد. (يمكنكم متابعة الدعم الإداري على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org)
Then let me see
دعني أرى
how well you can behave.
مدى قدرتك على التصرف بشكل جيد.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Getting scared now?
هل تشعر بالخوف الآن؟
That's a pity.
هذا مؤسف.
I don't like you at all.
أنا لا أحبك على الإطلاق.
Gu Yixiao,
قو ييشياو,
I know you like Xingyue.
أعلم أنك معجب بـ Xingyue.
She's sweet,
إنها لطيفة،
sensible,
منطقي،
and obedient.
ومطيع.
But before I met you,
لكن قبل أن ألتقي بك،
I was just like that too.
كنتُ كذلك أيضاً.
Ye Xingwan,
يي شينغوان،
don't use the tricks you play on those men
لا تستخدم الحيل التي تمارسها على هؤلاء الرجال
to deal with me.
أن يتعامل معي.
Go ahead.
تفضل.
What's your goal this time?
ما هو هدفك هذه المرة؟
I'm serious this time.
أنا جاد هذه المرة.
I don't want to be your socialite
لا أريد أن أكون من الطبقة الاجتماعية الخاصة بك
used to curry favor with the powerful anymore.
لم يعد الأمر يُستخدم لكسب ودّ الأقوياء.
I actually want to do real work.
أريد فعلاً أن أقوم بعمل حقيقي.
You want to get involved in my business?
هل ترغب في المشاركة في أعمالي؟
I want you to see what I'm capable of.
أريدك أن ترى ما أستطيع فعله.
What I can offer you
ما يمكنني تقديمه لك
is way more than you think.
الأمر أكبر بكثير مما تتخيل.
I know the company's been planning
أعلم أن الشركة كانت تخطط
an acquisition of an e-sports club.
الاستحواذ على نادٍ للرياضات الإلكترونية.
I can help you with that.
أستطيع مساعدتك في ذلك.
I'll think about it.
سأفكر في الأمر.
Then I'll stay here for now.
سأبقى هنا الآن.
(Wang Yaqin was right.)
(كان وانغ ياكين محقًا.)
(To win someone over, to win their heart.)
(لكسب ودّ شخص ما، لكسب قلبه.)
(This round,)
(في هذه الجولة،)
(I won.)
(لقد فزت.)
(Gu Group)
(مجموعة جو)
(Donghua University E-sports Club Acquisition Project)
(مشروع الاستحواذ على نادي الرياضات الإلكترونية بجامعة دونغوا )
(Access restricted: You have no permission)
(الوصول مقيد: ليس لديك إذن)
(So this acquisition isn't as simple as it looks.)
(إذن، عملية الاستحواذ هذه ليست بالبساطة التي تبدو عليها.)
(But where should I)
(ولكن أين ينبغي لي ذلك؟)
(get this internal data?)
(هل حصلت على هذه البيانات الداخلية؟)
Don't be in such a rush.
لا تتعجل.
He's not so foolish
إنه ليس أحمق إلى هذا الحد
to let you just easily
لتمكينك من ذلك بسهولة
find those key details.
ابحث عن تلك التفاصيل الرئيسية.
Anyway,
على أي حال،
I still want to thank you.
ما زلت أرغب في شكرك.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have noticed
وإلا لما كنت لاحظت ذلك
this acquisition plan.
خطة الاستحواذ هذه.
I have looked into a lot of information
لقد اطلعت على الكثير من المعلومات
and found no issues with this plan.
ولم أجد أي مشاكل في هذه الخطة.
So,
لذا،
the only explanation I can think of
التفسير الوحيد الذي يمكنني التفكير فيه
is money laundering.
غسيل الأموال.
I've heard
لقد سمعت
about Xu Dashan's matter.
بخصوص قضية شو داشان.
I've looked into you, Wang Yaqin.
لقد بحثت في أمرك يا وانغ ياكين.
Ever since Gu Group was founded,
منذ تأسيس مجموعة غو،
you've been here all along,
لقد كنت هنا طوال الوقت،
doing the toughest and dirtiest jobs.
القيام بأصعب وأقذر الأعمال.
But you never leaves this building.
لكنك لن تغادر هذا المبنى أبداً.
You even sleep in the storage room.
بل إنك تنام في غرفة التخزين.
What kind of grudge do you have against him?
ما نوع الضغينة التي تحملها ضده؟
That's none of your concern.
هذا ليس من شأنك.
Since
منذ
you've already moved into Gu Yixiao's villa,
لقد انتقلت بالفعل إلى فيلا غو ييشياو،
that proves what I said was right.
هذا يثبت صحة ما قلته.
Ever since I moved in,
منذ أن انتقلت إلى هنا،
he hasn't come back once.
لم يعد ولو لمرة واحدة.
He's always been a cautious man.
لطالما كان رجلاً حذراً.
For him,
بالنسبة له،
you need to be more patient.
عليك أن تتحلى بمزيد من الصبر.
You're just a cleaner,
أنت مجرد عامل نظافة،
yet you know so much
ومع ذلك فأنت تعرف الكثير
about what happens around Gu Yixiao.
حول ما يحدث حول غو ييشياو.
You're trying to get back at him.
أنت تحاول الانتقام منه.
Otherwise, why would you help me?
وإلا، فلماذا ستساعدني؟
That doesn't matter.
هذا لا يهم.
I'm helping you
أنا أساعدك
because I don't want to see him keep making mistakes.
لأنني لا أريد أن أراه يستمر في ارتكاب الأخطاء.
Maybe,
ربما،
you can actually save him.
بإمكانك إنقاذه بالفعل.
Miss Ye,
آنسة يي،
you know, between people,
كما تعلم، بين الناس،
there's more than just hate and pain.
الأمر يتجاوز مجرد الكراهية والألم.
Try opening his heart.
حاول أن تفتح قلبه.
Then you'll see a softer side
عندها سترى جانباً أكثر رقة
inside him.
داخله.
If everything you said is true,
إذا كان كل ما قلته صحيحاً،
wouldn't that softness be his weakness?
ألا يُعدّ هذا اللين نقطة ضعفه؟
Since you seem to know him so well,
بما أنك تبدو على دراية جيدة به،
can you tell me
هل يمكن أن تخبرني
what he actually likes?
ما الذي يحبه فعلاً؟
Mr. Chu,
السيد تشو،
you told me
أخبرتني
I could get Miss Ye.
بإمكاني الحصول على الآنسة يي.
But I ended up risking half my life.
لكن انتهى بي الأمر بالمخاطرة بنصف حياتي.
And we're just letting that go?
وهل نتجاهل ذلك ببساطة؟
Mr. Xu,
السيد شو،
this time, it was my fault.
هذه المرة، كان الخطأ خطئي.
This has nothing to do with Mr. Gu.
هذا لا علاقة له بالسيد غو.
I'll make up for your losses.
سأعوضك عن خسائرك.
Miss Ye,
آنسة يي،
I've been looking for you.
كنت أبحث عنك.
What do you want from me, Mr. Chu?
ماذا تريد مني يا سيد تشو؟
This is the acquisition proposal.
هذا هو مقترح الاستحواذ.
(E-sports Club Acquisition Proposal)
(مقترح الاستحواذ على نادٍ للرياضات الإلكترونية)
Mr. Gu asked me to give it to you.
طلب مني السيد غو أن أعطيه لك.
Don't be so proud.
لا تكن مغروراً جداً.
This is just the beginning.
هذه مجرد البداية.
What do you mean by that, Mr. Chu?
ماذا تقصد بذلك يا سيد تشو؟
Stop pretending it.
توقف عن التظاهر بذلك.
I know exactly what's on your mind.
أعرف تماماً ما يدور في ذهنك.
And I know what you're planning to do.
وأنا أعرف ما تخطط لفعله.
Right back at you.
وأنت كذلك.
If I told him about your plotting
لو أخبرته عن مؤامرتك
with Xu Dashan,
مع شو داشان،
what do you think
ماذا تعتقد؟
he would do?
ماذا سيفعل؟
Then I'll keep a close eye on you.
سأراقبك عن كثب حينها.
Let's wait and see.
لننتظر ونرى.
(Teaching Building)
(مبنى التدريس)
Ivan.
إيفان.
(Xiao Yinan)
(شياو ينان)
You know who I am?
هل تعرف من أنا؟
Captain of Dongda E-sports Team.
قائد فريق دونغدا للرياضات الإلكترونية.
Winner of the LVP National Finals.
الفائز في نهائيات الرابطة الوطنية لمحترفات الغولف.
Hot favorite for the next world championship.
المرشح الأبرز للفوز ببطولة العالم القادمة.
A true prodigy.
عبقري حقيقي.
I'm the secretary of Gu Group,
أنا سكرتيرة مجموعة غو،
Ye Xingwan.
يي شينغوان.
We need to talk in private.
نحتاج إلى التحدث على انفراد.
What do you mean by that?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
Exactly what it sounds like.
كما يبدو تماماً.
Our group plans to acquire your team.
تخطط مجموعتنا للاستحواذ على فريقكم.
Winning isn't the only goal.
الفوز ليس الهدف الوحيد.
There's also a business purpose behind it.
وهناك أيضاً غرض تجاري وراء ذلك.
As the captain,
بصفتي قائدًا،
you'll need to help us recruit new talent,
ستحتاج إلى مساعدتنا في استقطاب مواهب جديدة،
and expand the lineup.
وتوسيع التشكيلة.
As for our financial accounts,
أما بالنسبة لحساباتنا المالية،
during the review,
أثناء المراجعة،
just keep quiet, alright?
التزم الصمت، حسناً؟
You're breaking the law.
أنت تخالف القانون.
Why do you think I'd help you guys?
لماذا تعتقدون أنني سأساعدكم؟
If you have any terms, just say them.
إذا كانت لديك أي شروط، فقلها فقط.
You want money
تريد المال
or something else?
أم شيء آخر؟
What if I say no?
ماذا لو قلت لا؟
I don't want the team I built from scratch
لا أريد الفريق الذي بنيته من الصفر
to become someone's tool.
أن يصبح أداة في يد شخص ما.
Don't be so sure just yet.
لا تكن متأكداً جداً بعد.
Human nature cannot withstand tests.
لا تستطيع الطبيعة البشرية الصمود أمام الاختبارات.
When you say that,
عندما تقول ذلك،
you're basically admitting our offer
أنت بذلك تقر ضمنيًا بعرضنا
wasn't tempting enough.
لم يكن الأمر مغرياً بما فيه الكفاية.
Is that so?
هل هذا صحيح؟
So how much temptation are you going to give me?
إذن، ما مقدار الإغراء الذي ستمنحني إياه؟
What if I say
ماذا لو قلت
what I want is you?
ما أريده هو أنت؟
So young,
صغير جداً،
yet with quite a lot of ideas.
لكن مع وجود الكثير من الأفكار.
I never imagined
لم أتخيل ذلك أبداً
the person who once got into Donghua University's Faculty of Law,
الشخص الذي سبق له الالتحاق بكلية الحقوق بجامعة دونغوا،
determined to become a lawyer,
عازماً على أن يصبح محامياً،
would now be asking me to commit a crime with her.
الآن ستطلب مني أن أرتكب جريمة معها.
How do you know?
كيف علمت بذلك؟
Sis,
نعم،
don't you recognize me?
ألا تعرفني؟
♪The fragility stripped away by you♪
الهشاشة التي سلبتها منا؟
♪Keeps dragging me down endlessly♪
يستمر في إحباطي بلا نهاية.
♪If not once devoured by blazing flames♪
???إن لم تلتهمها النيران المشتعلة مرة واحدة؟؟؟
♪Who would ever understand this baptism by fire♪
من ذا الذي سيفهم هذه المعمودية بالنار؟
♪You betrayed me so decisively♪
لقد خنتني بشكل قاطع!
♪With indifference laid bare♪
???مع انكشاف اللامبالاة بوضوح؟
♪It taught me to stay silent first♪
لقد علمني ذلك أن ألتزم الصمت أولاً.
♪So the explosion would be deafening♪
إذن سيكون الانفجار مدوياً لدرجة الصمم؟
♪A burning soul tears off its own shackles♪
روح متقدة تمزق قيودها بنفسها.
♪The stubborn pain♪
الألم العنيد
♪Hardens into the hottest flame♪
يتحول إلى لهب شديد الحرارة.
♪Taste the fruit you planted, don't ask me for mercy♪
تذوق ثمرة ما زرعت، ولا تطلب مني الرحمة.
♪Just enjoy this searing pain♪
استمتع فقط بهذا الألم الحارق!
♪See whether blood or tears flow first♪
انظر أيهما يتدفق أولاً، الدم أم الدموع؟
♪Your screams sound like regret to me♪
صرخاتك تبدو لي كأنها ندم.
♪Greed caused the chaos, none can run away♪
الجشع هو سبب الفوضى، ولا أحد يستطيع الهرب.
♪The karma you sowed by your own hands♪
???الكارما التي زرعتها بيديك؟
♪Watered to maturity with blood and tears♪
???رُويت حتى نضجت بالدم والدموع؟ ???
♪Then ignite the anger forged by hatred♪
ثم أشعل الغضب الذي يولده الحقد.
♪I'll burn it all down♪
سأحرق كل شيء!